[Hidden deep in every corner of the vast island]
[Find and decode the ancient language]
[There can only be two princes]
The prince status will only be given to two.
Is it "CARAMEL"?
[The owners of the throne are revealed]
I was searching for ages!
Oh, I got it.
[Shin Dong & Johnny rise as princes]
I'm the prince!
[And the four left behind are paupers?!]
No! I'm the pauper!
[The game isn't over yet]
Time for an urgent announcement!
Through some games,
you'll get a chance
for a status upgrade today!
That's a good announcement!
[The real final chance for
these guys to upgrade their status]
[Only the winners will become commoners]
[Their competitiveness explodes]
Please…!
[Finally escaped his pauper status!]
Ji Sung gets a status upgrade!
[And soon]
DAWN gets a status upgrade!
[Dinner time for the two princes,
the two commoners, and the two paupers]
[The brutal status-based dinner
strikes again today]
Why does this taste so good?
[+The commoners are invited too]
[A final feast for the princes]
[Agony]
Ugh! It looks so delicious!!!
I want pizza so much right now…
Can we just dip it in the sauce?
[The paupers even resort to begging]
Can we please just dip it in the sauce?
Oh!! It fell!!
[Literally a pie in the sky for the paupers]
It fell!! It fell!!
Oh, why?
[Wait, don't we have ramyeon?!]
There's ramyeon left!
Oh, there's ramyeon!!
We can eat ramyeon in the tent, right?
[But]
A serious incident has happened.
[Their precious ramyeon has gone missing?!]
A Bowl Noodle Soup theft!
- What are you talking about?
- Who is it?
- If you get caught, there's no mercy.
- They said it's someone in here!
[The real culprit
who stole the ramyeon is among us]
[Lee Teuk]
[Shin Dong]
[DAWN]
[Johnny]
[Kim Yo Han]
[Ji Sung]
- Everyone, there's ramyeon left!
- Oh, right!
- Oh, there's ramyeon!!
- That's true!
[Super excited that there's ramyeon left]
We can eat ramyeon in the tent, right?
Even if we eat it now…
Don't bring that out yet!
They're all gonna eat it!
We were gonna eat that later
just by ourselves!
The production team
seriously can't read the room!
[Cluelessly brought all the remaining ramyeon]
[+Kimchi]
Alright, the remaining…
Oh, Kimchi!!!!
Take it out later!
We're gonna eat it in our tent!
[Merciful princes]
We'll give you a chance to eat it in the tent.
- We won't eat it.
- Oh, you're not eating it?
- Thank you.
- Enjoy it in the tent.
Thank you.
[Snapped back to reality]
But…
We brought the remaining cups of ramyeon.
Didn't you say there was Cup Ramyeon?
Yeah! The Bowl Noodle Soup.
We packed the Cup Ramyeon...
- But the Cup Ramyeon's gone!
- What?!
- It must've been the wind.
- Who did it?
- Someone must've taken it.
Who ate it...?
A serious incident has happened.
A Cup Ramyeon theft!
- Who is it?
- Seriously?
Lee Teuk.
[The culprit within us!]
Ugh, Lee Teuk! Seriously!
- If you get caught, there's no mercy.
- It's someone here.
[Suspect 1. Lee Teuk]
Wait a sec, Lee Teuk!
Wow, Lee Teuk, you ate it?
- Wow, this is legendary.
- During break time,
(Suspicious)
did you eat it? Be honest.
I'm literally skin and bones right now.
What could I have eaten?
This guy ate it!
[Wronged]
I seriously didn't eat it.
He ate it for sure.
You're the one who ate it!
Lee Teuk, did you eat it?
You're full right now, aren't you?
I'm full.
You ate it!!!
[Suspect 2. Shin Dong]
Shin Dong, did you eat the Bowl Noodle Soup?
I didn't eat it. I don't like ramyeon.
[Witness]
Shin Dong has been saying that!
I don't like ramyeon.
[A battle of suspicions]
Shin Dong ate it.
- I didn't eat it, for real.
- Look, look.
[Suspicious]
Lee Teuk, why are you accusing him?
No, look…!
DAWN definitely didn't eat anything!
- He's eating now because he's hungry.
- Of course.
[Ji Sung is also ruled out]
Ji Sung didn't eat it either.
How could I eat this
after having ramyeon?
The culprit is one of the princes!
No!
- The culprit is…
- Either Shin Dong or Johnny.
[Is Shin Dong or Johnny the culprit?]
Seeing how he's framing us…
Because…
the younger guys wouldn't
even dare dream of doing that.
- That's true.
- Yeah.
They wouldn't even dare think about it.
Honestly, it's gotta be
either Shin Dong or Lee Teuk.
Should we play a round of Mafia with this setup?
- Shall we do it?
- For real?
It's you, huh?
Johnny!
I'm way younger than you.
How could I even mess with that?
That's pretty suspicious, though?
[Great acting or actually innocent…?]
Hey, let's not play dirty
over something like this.
Ji Sung, is it you?
I don't really like
that ramyeon much.
[Right?]
I like the Omori ramyeon.
If it's one of the princes,
let's strip them of their prince title!
What if it's one of the paupers?
[That's a sharp question]
Sleep without a tent?
I can't sleep without a tent…
Lee Teuk ate it!
He said he can't sleep without a tent.
[Closing in on the suspect…?]
Oh, seriously, here…
- You end up getting caught over things like this.
- No, it's not me!
["If I'm the culprit…?" Pledge announcement!]
Then say, "If it's really me,"
and each make a pledge.
- If I ate it…!
- If I ate it…?
- What are you willing to stake?
- Exactly!
I'll go last!
[Shin Dong makes his pledge first]
I'll go first.
If I ate the Bowl Noodle Soup,
on the flight back to Korea,
[For the flight home: Giving up business class]
I'll give up my business class seat completely.
I'll fly economy.
Huh? He's being for real then.
Shin Dong finds the seats super uncomfortable.
You can trust me with this, right?
I know Shin Dong well,
so the fact that he's saying that…
Okay, DAWN.
[DAWN's pledge is?]
Wow, this is really… But that was a strong one.
If I ate that Cup Ramyeon...!
If you ate it?
First, that just doesn't make any sense.
- And?
- What?
- Huh?
- No, I mean, I…
Hey, was it you?
[Wow, is it unexpectedly DAWN?]
Is it surprisingly him?
Come on, Shin Dong. If I ate the ramyeon,
would I have eaten this much food?
You've been eating a lot lately.
He kept eating so we wouldn't suspect him!
- Was it you?
- Really?
[Playing the broke card]
I've got nothing to bet.
- If I ate it…!
- Yeah?
This TABASCO sauce…
I'll pour it into a soju glass and down it!
I think anyone could do that.
[That's a weak pledge]
You could just drink that.
If I drink that wrong,
I could literally die.
Okay, Yo Han.
Firstly, I didn't eat it!
If I ate it…!
I have to sleep
in the tent tonight, right?
I'll sleep outside the tent,
wrapped in a sleeping bag!
Sleeping outdoors.
[Yo Han's pledge: Sleep outside the tent]
Sleeping outside the tent?
- Yes, yes.
- Okay!
Yo Han, don't you like that kind of thing?
I don't like it.
I like beds too.
- Oh, really???
- Johnny.
- If it's me…
- Yeah.
I'll take a quick dip in the Red Sea!
[Right now?]
Like right now?
[I'll run to the Red Sea right now]
I'll run there now!
- For real?
- For real.
That was gonna be my pledge…
[Ji Sung's turn]
Okay! Ji Sung.
[Wow…]
If I am the culprit...
[Ssp…]
- Was it you?
- Ji Sung's already acting shady.
[Slap]
[Fiddling]
Ji Sung, it's all okay.
But I guess when
you can't think of a pledge,
everyone reaches for the hot sauce.
Then!
I'll just take this pasta,
[Mix the pasta with hot sauce and eat it?]
mix this in and eat all of it?
- That sounds so good!
- Seriously, hot sauce!
If you ate the Cup Ramyeon,
can you become a pauper?!
I can't…
- Huh?
- Oh, if I ate it…
If… If I ate it…
I didn't eat it, so...
It's you, huh?
[Stammering]
The Cup Ramyeon... As a commoner…
What are you even talking about right now?
- Oh, but, like…
- Ji Sung's bad at lying!
But pauper… I mean, doesn't it mean
I don't become a pauper?
No. It means you will become a pauper.
- If you ate the Bowl Noodle Soup…
- That means you become a pauper.
[The paupers]
Then 3 people will sleep in the tent.
Can you become a pauper?
If you ate it?
Oh, I can't.
I don't want to be a pauper.
- Then that means you ate it!
How did it get like this?
- If you didn't eat it, you don't become a pauper.
- If you did, you can't bet on it.
If you ate it, you become a pauper.
[Ji Sung, was it you?]
Oh, was it you?
[Caught the ramyeon thief]
[Everyone except the culprit stands up]
Hey, was it you?
- Wow! Who is this guy?
- Wow, seriously!
Hey!
- Hey!
- Hey, Ji Sung!
It wasn't even your team's ramyeon!
It was our team's!
- What's up with this guy?
- Seriously!
[Stayed quiet all this time to act up at the end]
Hey, that Bowl Noodle Soup was mine!
- Wait a second!
- What's up with this guy?
You have such an innocent face,
[Slurping ramyeon from behind]
but behind our backs...
I didn't eat it...
[It's too late now, Ji Sung]
What do you mean you didn't eat it? It's over!
Ji Sung!
[Tear drop…]
Hey, what's up with this guy?
Hey, who are you?
- Were you really this kind of person?
- Betrayal!
Is this who you really are?
Are you pulling
the hermit crab move right now?
Just be honest with us.
[Confess the truth]
If you ate it, you can just say you did.
I ate it.
[What is happening
all of a sudden…]
Wait, what's this about?
I'm really flustered…
Didn't someone say that earlier?
- The younger guys wouldn't dare to do it?
- I…
- I definitely wouldn't!
- Hey, what have you been teaching him?
[He's the youngest]
I messed up.
- You're seriously hilarious.
- This is unbelievable.
I automatically assumed
it was one of the SUPER JUNIOR members.
- For real!
- I was sure it was Lee Teuk!
[Fired up]
Hey, why are you suspecting me?
- Lee Teuk really likes ramyeon.
- That's just been your track record so far!
I like ramyeon, but I don't steal things!
But if you ate it, you would've eaten
something else, not the Cup Ramyeon.
- No wonder he came out wearing a beanie.
- I know, right?
[Metaphor for a culprit]
I guess Ji Sung really wanted to win.
- He wanted to eat, get energy, and win.
- It's okay. It's okay with Ji Sung.
[WANGGEOZ group toast]
Alright, let's raise our glasses together.
Congrats, Ji Sung.
- Hold on, hold on.
- What's going on?
- What's this?
- Among us…
- Yeah, among us?
- There's one more mafia member!
Someone else ate with you?
It's Johnny!
You two were together!
[Can't let this slide!]
Let's just really play the Mafia game now.
It wasn't me.
We weren't even in the same room.
[But what if you are the accomplice?]
So if it is you…
- I said I'll go in the water!
- You'll go in?
Was it you?
I'm sorry!
[Caught the accomplice]
Hot sauce!
- Drink the hot sauce!!!
- No wonder!
[The hot sauce pledge was already strange...]
No wonder! This amount is totally doable!
You should've said
you'd pour it all in and drink it!
[They get more annoyed as they think about it]
I had a feeling it was him!
- But he suddenly…!
- Sorry!
- You two ate it?
- Yes.
[A minor commotion among the commoners]
Oh, the two commoners. Okay.
[The pauper is mad]
Then strip the commoners of their titles!
Revoke it!
Should we do it?
This is the prince's authority!
[Defending himself]
We didn't pledge that! We didn't!
[All or nothing!]
All King and All Pauper, just go be a pauper!
Just do it!
Nice!
Let's do it!
But I do actually like
having a room to myself.
Come on!
Shin Dong, I'll stay in the bathroom then!
[Throwing a tantrum]
Make all four of us paupers!
Just two is too lonely!
Four paupers sleeping together
is better than two.
[Makes total sense the more they listen]
- It's so great! - All cozy together.
Exactly!
You got to enjoy all the food.
I'll go empty myself out.
Empty what?
Then we'll wait for the princes' decision.
- The princes' decision is…!
- Please show leniency!
- Please!
Oh, why? A final closing argument...?
- I will make the closing argument!
- The closing argument!
Yes.
DAWN was the one who first…
[The enabler]
Wow, this…!
[I beg for leniency]
Wow…!
Please only punish DAWN!
DAWN's never even slept in a tent!
[I don't want to…lose my commoner status]
Should we send DAWN away?
Wow, Ji Sung must be really desperate.
My rebuttal!
I really felt bad for Ji Sung. Really!
You all saw earlier!
[Shivering]
He was shivering.
Yeah, so the ramyeon…
But!!!!!! Do you know what's really important?!
That Bowl Noodle Soup was totally mine!
DAWN, that Bowl Noodle Soup was mine.
- Oh, really?
- It was mine.
Was it DAWN who brought up
eating the Cup Ramyeon?
Wasn't it you?
[The culprits start fighting each other]
Who was it?
Just be honest.
[Only one of the two survives]
Only one of the two…!
We'll only send one of you!
Huh? Was it me?
"Huh, was it me?"
Let's play it back!
Was there no camera?
[VAR]
Okay, you two
[Let's review the video]
Can we get a little help with the ramyeon?
[The culprits were running
the princes' ramyeon errand]
Should we secretly
eat one before we go?
[Fact check 1]
I think no one will notice, right?
[DAWN suggested it first]
If we eat it right away and go?
I looked at Ji Sung,
and he looked way too gaunt.
[This big brother]
As his older brother,
I have to take care of him!
[Gonna eat ramyeon]
Oh, we should eat ramyeon together.
(Definitely not because he wanted to eat it)
[The devil's whisper continues]
Since the noodles take time to cook anyway.
- Should we eat it?
- Wait.
[Fact check 2]
[Ji Sung agreed too]
[Target spotted]
Should we eat the Bowl Noodle Soup?
This Bowl Noodle Soup too…
I feel like no one would notice.
Since the noodles take time to cook,
let's just eat one here!
Let's split one between us.
But shouldn't we cook this one too?
[Yeah, we have to cook it first]
Let's cook it fast!
- We'll pour the hot water in this one first.
- Oh, okay, okay.
[There's no turning back now]
[Ji Sung turns into a meerkat]
(Definitely not because DAWN wanted to eat it)
The water's finally warm.
We have to hurry and eat this first, so…
[No time to wait for the water to boil]
This…
[Starting to justify the crime]
This is all part of the fun.
[Ready to eat just 1 minute after pouring water]
It's a bit undercooked, though...
[Basically raw]
I'm all about that chewy texture.
Me too, I also really love it that way.
[Flinching at the slightest breeze]
[You are watching the ramyeon heist in action]
Let's dig in.
[The magic of instant happiness]
This is insanely good.
[Pure bliss]
[Took a bite, when someone showed up]
Wow, seriously...!
I thought it was Shin Dong.
Oh, Director!
I thought you were Shin Dong!
I thought it was Shin Dong!
[Audio crew appears (to check the mics)]
[Even though they feel uneasy
and their ramyeon is lukewarm]
But isn't this seriously so delicious?
[Happy ramyeon thieves]
But seriously, this place…
[Hehehehehehehe]
It was a bit crunchy,
but eating in secret made it so delicious.
Shin Dong said it earlier, remember?
- Ramyeon tastes the best when you eat it in secret.
- I know, right?
- We're just doing what he said.
- We're just listening to the king.
[Getting more shameless by the minute]
Exactly.
[Casually savoring the broth too]
Hey, the broth is next level.
[Finally coming to his senses]
But, this must be soggy by now.
- I think we should go now.
- Yeah, let's go, let's go.
Let me throw away the broth.
Wanna throw it away in my body instead?
Oh, this, this!
- I'll…
- Oh, you're gonna drink it?
[The best cleanup method is]
[eating it all up!]
But seriously, it's so good.
[Exhibit 1]
We gotta throw away the trash properly.
[Ramyeon trash]
Can we just hide it like this?
[Evidence disposal complete]
Oh, okay. It's over there.
- Check your lips.
- Lemme see, lemme see.
[Exhibit 2]
Wait, you got some on you.
[Ji Sung has ramyeon traces around his mouth]
Hold on.
[Evidence wiped clean]
[Sweet DAWN]
Oh, it's fine, it's fine.
[Even when they all ate ramyeon together]
This is just too good.
This is seriously delicious.
[Giving his best salivating performance]
This is really…
There's not much left.
[and fake act of desperation]
Wow!
What about me?
[Scraping the bottom of the bowl for show]
- You scrape at it even if there's nothing.
- You end up scraping at it.
I barely ate, but I feel full.
- We only had a bite, but we feel full, right?
- Yeah.
[Because we ate earlier]
[Even while talking about the ramyeon]
What else is left over?
[Cup Ramyeon!]
Bowl Noodle Soup.
Bowl Noodle Soup and…
[Eye contact]
If you add perilla powder to Bowl Noodle Soup,
[LOL]
it tastes like pork bone soup.
[Desperately trying to keep a straight face]
- Oh, really? - Yeah.
I ate way too much
Bowl Noodle Soup back in Korea.
[Playing dumb to avoid getting caught]
Thanks for the food.
Then, when you were running our errand?
Yeah!
- We ate it while making your ramyeon.
- Yeah, that's right.
[Finally confessing openly]
Oh, then! That's when you ate it?
We ate it with cold, lukewarm water.
You're unbelievable.
Well, as for me,
[Sweeping the past under the rug]
I don't dwell on the past.
Is that so?
- Your Honor!
- Yes!
- Are you the judge?
- Yes, I'm the judge.
[Court is in session at the dinner table]
- Your Honor. - Yes.
- As the pauper team's counsel…
- Yes.
we ask that DAWN sleeps with us.
[We want DAWN, the culprit!]
What are you talking about?
- That's not even in the rules.
- Alright!
[Rushing to judgment]
What do you mean by "Alright", Shin Dong?
[Already ready to deliver the verdict]
Please don't do that, seriously.
Alright!
- Now that it's come to this…
- Come to this?
we can't just let them off
without any punishment.
Please give them a punishment!
Right, so…
They were upgraded to commoners,
[To undo all that is a bit…]
but taking back the titles feels a bit…
- Absolutely not!
- So!
So! Okay!
We, the princes,
[Prince Court Final Verdict]
have gathered everyone's opinions,
- and sentence DAWN…!
- DAWN!
to 1 hour of pauper life.
[Order]
[The defendant is sentenced to 1 hour as a pauper]
[Objection]
1 hour is too short!
So that he can
at least experience the tent…!
Honorable Judge!
I will not receive any more honor.
- Less-honorable Judge!
- Yes.
I object!!
Is this "The Truman Show" or what? Seriously!
1 hour is just not enough!
What's not enough?
1 hour is plenty!
[An impassioned plea]
1 hour really isn't enough!
In 1 hour, the stock market
can fluctuate several times!
Please, let me
share a tent with DAWN.
This court is adjourned!
[Bang! Bang! Bang!]
No! No!
- This trial is invalid!!!!
- Thank you!
[Thank you for the leniency]
I'll work hard from now on!
- Thank you!
- Oh, come on!
[Deeply invested]
The justice system is rotten!
What came to mind while playing the games…
I should've gone
to make the ramyeon myself...
I should've made the ramyeon...
and eaten 2 cups of ramyeon.
If I'd known I'd end up a pauper
and not get to eat anything,
I should've just gone and eaten
everything I wanted before coming back...
[A day filled with late regrets]
Yeah, I'm regretting it a bit.
This is why I never share
a table with the paupers!
[Table Courtroom]
[Crime and Ramyeon]
[The End]
This is seriously hilarious. Wow.
But where are we even sleeping?
The original place we chose
for the paupers to set up the tent was…
You saw it earlier
while searching for clues.
[During "Conversations with the Ancients"]
You know, that rocky hill?
- No, not there!
- That was the original spot?
That was the original spot.
We'll really get blown away there…
Seeing today's wind,
we thought it wouldn't work out.
We can't, we can't.
So we prepared a place
that's safer and flatter.
- Where? Where's that?
- Where exactly?
The stairs that you came up on.
Wait, hold on.
[The paupers are sleeping on the stairs]
That's way better, way better.
Honorable…
If you look at the stairs going down,
there's one unusually big step.
- Oh, in the middle.
- Oh, there, there!
Honorable Producer!
[The highly respectful type]
I formally object!
The stone part over there
could hurt our bones, right?
We'll lay down a padded mat for you anyway.
- I've been a pauper a few times now, right?
- Yes.
[2-time pauper]
There is a padded mat.
Right.
[1-time pauper]
I know that too!
- You know?
- Honorable Producer!
Our sleeping spot…!
Even ghosts look better
on a full stomach!
[We will sleep at the restaurant]
We will sleep right here.
Lee Teuk, this place is even windier!
No, because there's a partition down here.
Lee Teuk, I'm sitting right next to it, right?
It's super windy right here!
[But it's blowing sand down there…]
I think it'd be better here, because..
- The wind's blowing so much sand over there.
- Exactly!
[On point]
- But you're pitching tents. - That's true...
When we decide on a place,
we have one rule we try to stick to.
[Paupers' accommodation rule]
- What kind of rule? - No roofs allowed.
The stars are our blankets!
Can't we do a little location scouting first?
[Princes' mercy]
We'll allow some location scouting.
Just make sure to follow that one rule.
[Paupers' accommodation rule 1]
Right, you can't have a roof.
- No roofs?
- Yes.
[Paupers' accommodation rule 2]
You can't sleep somewhere higher than the princes.
[Royal approval]
Didn't you just make up the second rule?
[Correct!]
[The princes will head to their comfy quarters]
Alright, the princes will go now.
Where are you going?
We're going to our rooms.
See you in an hour, DAWN.
Okay!
- Let's go!
- Yeah, let's go!
Did you sell me out because
you were scared of becoming a pauper?
[Sorry]
[Biggest beneficiary]
Thank goodness, it's just probation!
Oh, it's cold!
[As if it were planned, the paupers remain]
[Munch, munch...]
This is seriously delicious.
[Fries forever]
Wow, they left all of this?!
Those pauper-like fools!
[Glare]
[Pauper to pauper]
Those pauper-like fools! Leaving food behind!
[Scolding]
You will pay for this!
You'll be forced to eat
all of this in the afterlife!
[Classic boomer energy]
Kids these days have no drive! No grit!
They don't even know
what tear-soaked bread tastes like.
Excuse me.
Microwave, heat up!
[Rich accent]
Please heat it up!
Ugh… So cold…
Ugh, seriously!!
This is going too far!
[Yo Han, stuff your face first]
(Trembling)
[Calm again]
But this is really good.
[Eating every last crumb]
Yo Han, make sure to grab the water.
Oh, the water!
Lee Teuk, other than Day 1,
this is your first time as a pauper, right?
[Lol...]
It's all about how you
start and finish,
but both my start and finish
were a total disaster.
Oh, right! That's true, Lee Teuk.
- Let's go.
- Lee Teuk, let's go check out the site!
Let's go.
(Commoner's bed) (Prince's bed)
I'm wondering…
[Johnny & Ji Sung]
[Chilling together]
Should we sleep with this open or closed?
[Leave it open]
Totally…!
I'm gonna catch the sunrise.
- You're gonna watch the sunrise…?
- Yeah.
Why?
I'm curious, you know,
being on an island like this...
[First day as a commoner]
What time's the sunrise?
[Comfort brings out his romantic side]
Around 5 or 6 am.
Let me check…
Egypt...
[Heh...]
Heh, like...
[So obvious]
"Egypt sunrise time."
[Correct]
[On the same wavelength]
I just got goosebumps.
[If you wanna see the sunrise,
better sleep quickly]
- Wanna do a face pack?
- Nah!
I'm good.
[Self-care king]
I'm gonna do it!
[Finally lying down on
my small, precious bed]
You're tired, huh?
Yeah, tired but feeling great.
I can't believe I'm not in a tent…!
[Even though his tentmates kept rotating out,]
[Ji Sung was always present in the tent…]
(Resident ghost)
[Johnny leaves to shower first]
I'll go wash up.
Okay.
[Yaaaaaawn]
[Oh, right]
I need to check the sunrise time.
(Egypt... sunrise... time...)
[Current time 11:42 pm]
Wow, 5:13 is way too brutal.
Then I'll...
Since the sunrise is at 5:13...
I'll wake up around 5.
[Hmm...]
[Not feeling confident]
[Let's just lie down first]
[Plops!]
What I'm seeing over there
can't be a mosquito, right…?
[The biggest crisis for the bug hater]
[Oh my goodness…]
Whoa! Head rush…
Orthostatic hypotension...
(I need to check
what kind of bug that is…)
[It's definitely a bug...]
I'm pretty sure…
(Glance)
[Failed to keep a brave front]
(Ha... if it falls on the bed…)
[Uh-oh]
[Giving up]
Let's just sleep...
[While Ji Sung's spiraling over the bug]
But instead of going there,
why not go over here on the sand…
[The criminal and paupers inspect the site]
Because the tent needs to stay up.
[Location conditions]
Where should we really sleep?
[No roof allowed]
[Lower than the princes' accommodation]
Lee Teuk, you choose!
[Hard rock floor]
Do you prefer firm beds?
[vs Soft sandy floor]
Or do you like soft beds?
Since you have the most
pauper experience here...
[Pauper: 2 / Pauper: 0 / Pauper: 3]
I was basically an ALL-Pauper.
- Yeah, since you have the most experience…
- Yes.
You tell me where it's better to sleep.
[Yo Han's pick: hard rock floor]
I definitely think it's better to sleep here,
because, we've got mats, right?
[Basic option: 2 toppers]
Lay down 2 of them.
[Extra option: 1 sleeping bag per person]
And then we add sleeping bags.
- Okay.
- So,
[Current pauper leader makes the call]
the floor may be hard, but it's flat.
- Yeah, that's right.
- Yes.
[I'm counting on you, Yo Han]
Let's set it out here.
[Setting up the tent in the strong winds]
Are we setting it up now?
But DAWN's never set up a tent before.
This is totally…
[3-time prince DAWN is new to the tent]
It's my first time doing this.
This might blow away, so be careful.
This…
[The veteran paupers show how it's done]
Like this, then like that.
You have to line up the joints right.
- It's the other way around. This goes on top.
- Redo it, redo it.
[Wiiiiiind]
Oh, it's turning around!
We have to hold it down!
We have to hold it down…
[Heavy supplies incoming]
And the mat goes in!
[A quick emergency fix]
[Our home can't fly away…!]
Sleeping bag, sleeping bag!
(Struggling)
Put these on both sides like this.
Like this.
(Hmm...)
[Quickly bailing]
I think it's been an hour already.
[Disappointed]
DAWN, it's only been 2 minutes.
Oh, really?
Come on in!
Welcome to our humble home!
[A not-so-exciting invitation]
Let's have a fun time.
[Actual floor space]
Wow, it's pretty spacious.
- Yeah, come on in.
- Three people can sleep here comfortably.
But when you come in,
please make sure to organize your shoes.
[Grumpy]
Yeah.
[I'm not planning to sleep here…]
I'll be heading out soon anyways…
(Neatly placed)
No, you should sleep over!
[Coming in is up to you,]
You're free to come in whenever you want,
[but leaving is up to me]
but when it comes to leaving…
- Oh, really?
- Yeah.
[Regret]
I shouldn't have eaten that ramyeon…
[Quickly settling in]
But now that I'm here,
- it's a bit less cold…
- Right?
You can even see the moon.
[Blocked]
You can even see the stars...
[It's still kinda romantic...?]
The view's nice. It's quite romantic, Lee Teuk.
[Commoner DAWN, completely zoning out]
[and the paupers,
feeling hopeless about their future]
(Let's try it this way)
[Leg stretch]
[Trying anything to survive]
Like this?
- Sleep like this.
- Like this, like this.
- With this kind of vibe.
[Chills]
Wow, but this is dangerous...
There's a cactus right in front of us.
[Dangerous]
If it falls, it'll land right on us.
I don't think I can sleep.
Yo Han! Is today the hardest day
in your pauper life?
- Yeah, today's definitely the hardest...
- Oh, really?
Were you a pauper
on the second day too?
I've been a pauper
straight since the second day.
- Oh, non-stop?
- Yeah.
[Pauper accommodation #2 was just romantic]
Honestly, the first time on the rooftop
was quite romantic.
The second one was
right in front of the cruise.
[Pauper accommodation #3 with a Nile River view]
That spot was pretty nice, too.
It was a bit lonely,
but it still felt like we were part of the cruise.
But that night
was the absolute worst of the worst.
This might not show well on camera,
but the wind was so strong
that when you sat or stood up,
it pushed your body back.
That island is literally an island of the wind.
I thought Lee Teuk and Yo Han
couldn't possibly sleep there.
But honestly,
it didn't really matter.
I just wanted to leave as soon as possible.
Should we try blocking it with this?
[Let's just try anything]
Wait, I think we need to fix this a bit.
[Zipping up the window to survive]
Is it good now?
[A ray of hope!]
Oh, it's not flying off...?
We can totally sleep in this!
It got way better.
This tent is really sturdy!
[Running away]
Oh, wait!
Hey! Hey!
Hey…
[Stepped out for a second, and the tent's flying]
Hey! Wait!
- Oh, wait!
- Wait, wait, wait, wait!
No, no!
[Wide open]
No, Lee Teuk…
[Snap]
Uh, wait a sec!
- Agh, Lee Teuk!!!
- Uh, wait a sec!
- Oh, our house!!!!!!
[On the verge of losing their shelter]
Put it down… Doesn't it move this way? Right?
(Glance)
It's this.
Look over there.
Look at the prince's accommodation over there.
You okay there?
Please let us sleep there
for just one night!
[Can't hear]
[No guarantees]
Will we be okay tomorrow?
Wow, this is seriously the worst it's ever been.
Let's just go inside for now.
[Re-entering as the wind dies down]
Ugh, I don't even know anymore.
[The remaining cups of ramyeon
make an appearance]
Here you go.
We'll eat now, Your Highness!
[We'll eat now, Commoner]
Me too.
I'm a pauper for an hour, too.
(Instant block)
Hey, stay back! What are you doing?
You already ate, DAWN.
[Extremely territorial paupers]
What's up with you?
After I ate earlier,
I didn't see this one!
Hey, what are you doing
in a pauper's tent right now?
Is this how you treat your guests?
You must maintain
your dignity, Your Highness!
[You must maintain
your dignity, Commoner]
[Only at times like this...]
Come on, now!
(Taking care of his little pauper brother first)
Here, take a pair of chopsticks.
I've got a favor. If you help me out,
I'll give you the chopsticks.
[A pauper's secret plea to the commoner]
Oh, what is it?
Right now, we…
[Ready to receive]
As you can see,
- if we sleep here and wake up tomorrow...
- Yeah?
One of us is definitely not gonna be here.
I saw that both of
the princes' rooms have terraces.
(Here)
Oh, there's a terrace.
[We can't sleep here]
So that we can pitch our tents on the terrace,
[Help us get permission]
please go up there with me to tell them.
Help us, okay?
- You want me to tell them
- Yeah.
about these miserable conditions, right?
[If you do, you can have first dibs on the ramyeon]
If you tell them, we'll let you have first dibs
on whatever you want to eat.
[Deal]
- Got it! - Oh, seriously?
[Agreement reached]
I did witness your miserable conditions.
Nice, okay.
[The ramyeon is finally ready]
I'll eat it first.
[Slurping up the perfectly cooked noodles]
[And topping it off
with some stir-fried Kimchi]
Wow!
[Chief negotiator DAWN takes a bite too]
[Fiery]
I wanted something spicy so badly!
DAWN, are you gonna eat Kimchi?
No, I'm not.
Then...
[Kimchi added]
I'm gonna put it in!
Kimchigetti!
(Inhaling the food)
Wow…!
[Touched]
Wow, this is seriously delicious...
(Eating well despite the awkward posture)
I wanna mix rice with this.
[In the midst of unimaginably strong winds,]
[the paupers scarf down the food…]
[along with the commoner]
[The Kimchi ends up inside a shoe]
Wait, the shoe…!
[Shocked]
Oh, jeez…
A lot of Kimchi went in there…!
[The chaos never stops at the pauper's house]
There's way more Kimchi juice
in here than I thought!
Tomorrow, my feet are gonna smell…
They're gonna smell like Kimchi!
If you're like, "It smells like Kimchi,"
- just know that it's me.
- Got it, got it.
You know what I mean?
- After living like this one time…
- Yes?
[DAWN experienced
the pauper life for the first time]
- It's kind of…
- Fun?
There's a sense of camaraderie.
So I'll go up there
and quickly pitch the idea to them.
[He wants to get out of here quickly]
[It was a great deal]
Okay, great!
[Quickly escaping the strong winds]
Alright, let's go.
[And heading out to beg the princes]
I'll hold the back.
Let's go!
Just go!
[Wiiiiiiind]
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
[My house is falling apart]
It's falling apart, it's falling apart!
[My precious home...]
Whoa!
I think we need to fold it here.
[They have to fold the tent first
before they do anything else]
I'm holding onto it.
How did you take that off?
That thing…
You have to press this here.
Oh, watch your hand!
Watch your hand!
[Snap]
Huh…?
It's not broken, right...?
[It is broken]
Oh! It's broken!
(Why is he like this…)
- Lee Teuk! - Nah, but this…
It can still stand!
[With the main pole snapping apart]
It can still stand.
- Are you sure?
- Yeah.
[They lose their only shelter]
Why did this break?
The tent got damaged there, and…
Ssp…
It turned into an unavoidable situation...
[We gotta go beg!]
So we went to beg again.
Paupers aren't paupers for nothing.
[The petition begins]
Your High…
Your Highness…!
Your Highness!
[Prince Shin Dong gets up
at the commotion outside the palace]
(What's all this noise?)
We need help!
[Help us, Prince]
The wind's blowing so hard…
The tent broke!
[The wind drowns out the paupers' voices]
I can't hear a word you're saying!
Come on up!
[We're on our way to beg…!]
We're on our way!
Oh, okay!
We got it, we got it.
[Heading up to meet the prince]
Shall we go?
Let's go, let's go!
[Following Commoner DAWN]
Everyone, follow me.
[are the two homeless paupers]
[On the way to appeal to Prince Shin Dong]
- Your Highness!
- Come on in.
[Escaping the wind and entering the palace]
Quickly come in! Quickly!
- Your Highness.
- Quickly come in.
Your Highness,
your citizens have requested to meet you.
What on earth happened?
It was brutal.
[The citizens who survived catastrophic winds]
The wind was blowing so hard.
- It's scary even just being in here.
- Right?
The wind is no joke.
Shin Dong, are you not wearing anything?
[Don't misunderstand]
- No, I am. - Oh, you were.
- Oh, they're pajamas?
- They're my royal pajamas.
- I thought it was just your bare skin.
- Oh, really?
So, what do you want me to do about it?
[Prince Shin Dong, please hear us out]
Go ahead and tell me.
I think we need to explain the entire story.
We asked the Commoner for a favor.
[Because the whole house flew away]
Since it was blowing away…
Since the tent was blowing away,
[Trying to move to the prince's terrace]
we wanted to ask to set it up here.
[It was when they were carrying the tent up here]
So, we were carrying the tent up…
We were carrying
the whole thing in one piece.
[The winds got even stronger]
But over there,
the winds got stronger the higher we climbed up.
You should've folded
the tent before bringing it up!
And so!
- We were gonna fold it here.
- We were gonna fold it.
- While folding it…
- Did it break?
We were folding it, but the wind
pressed down on it, and it snapped.
[They really became paupers
with nowhere to sleep]
(So what?)
What do you want me to do about it?
What do you mean?
Could you maybe let us
sleep in your bedroom tonight?
[Sneaking in their main request]
I'd love to, but there's no room here.
[Please let us sleep
anywhere in the prince's room…]
Can we come here and sleep?
Of course!
[Just sleep anywhere]
If there's a place, just sleep wherever.
[Compassion]
Just anywhere?
Sure! But, wait,
you have to pay for the tent.
[Quickly throwing him under the bus]
Lee Teuk broke it.
I broke it?
[Tends to set the record straight]
Was it me? I broke it?
Okay, okay. I'll…
I'll work it off somehow.
[The citizens' request has been granted]
It really can't be helped.
Please sleep inside tonight.
- Thank you! Thank you so much!
- As long as there's space.
[Thank you, Your Highness]
Thank you!
He...
[My savior, Prince Shin Dong]
Saved our lives!
He saved us.
- Hurry and sleep.
- Oh, yeah.
- Is the Commoner sleeping here?
- No, I'm…
- This is his spot.
- Oh, really?
This is my spot.
[Commoner will sleep beside the prince's bed]
Thank you.
Go find out first.
[The paupers head out to find a room]
Thank you!
Get some rest.
Goodbye!
[Will they find a place to sleep tonight…?]
Where are we supposed to go?
[Meanwhile, in the peaceful NCTZ's room]
[The bed is way too short]
Do you just want to
share the bed with me?
[Worried about the youngest sleeping cramped up]
Is it comfortable? You okay?
I mean, I'm okay.
But if we share a bed,
I think you'll be uncomfortable.
[As expected, the cool guy from Chicago]
I'm fine.
Not a big deal.
I'm really fine with it,
but I'm just worried about one thing.
- I kind of…
- Toss and twirl?
Twist and turn?
- Turn and toss?
- Kind of.
[It's not like you're gonna hug me…]
It's okay.
It's not like you'll hug me while you sleep.
So what are you gonna do?
Are you gonna come on the bed?
[Should I?]
[The commoner gets a bed upgrade]
Now that I'm a prince,
it's nice to even have time for a face mask.
Paupers only get
the humidifying masks at this hour.
[Thinking back on their dinner earlier]
So, about dinner earlier…
Since it's the last day,
I thought we'd just mess around
for about 10 minutes and then eat together.
But after seeing that
the paupers didn't get anything…
Seriously, wow…!
What's fun about this show is…
I'm not really competitive.
But here, I don't want to lose.
Just think about it.
[Always doing my best]
When we were in Luxor…
That was insane.
I was kind of moved then.
I actually ran a bit that day
because of you.
- Oh, really?
- Yeah.
I was pretty serious about it.
[Johnny & Ji Sung's Pillow Talk Show]
But when you're alone,
[The conversation topic]
Do I react when I'm alone?
[Do you react when you're alone?]
Yeah, you don't, right?
You don't, right? You don't?
[NCT 127 member]
But someone like Doyoung…
does when he's alone.
Oh?
[Wait a minute…]
Do I do that too…?
[Yes, you do. A lot]
Nice!
It's an emergency…
This is legendary...
I don't do it.
But these days,
no matter what it is,
I try to enjoy it more.
And honestly, when you do that,
- it hits you so much harder.
- I agree. I felt it too.
[Making an effort to enjoy something
makes it more memorable]
When I heard
we were coming to Egypt,
I contemplated for about 10 minutes.
I'm really glad I came.
- You're glad you came?
- Yeah.
But…
This was truly a proper trip, in a way.
More than just visiting the Temple,
- we actually played a game at the Temple.
- We played a game.
So,
even if people came here to travel,
they can't experience it like we did.
[A trip made special by enjoying the moment]
- That's true. - That's why we enjoyed it so much.
I think it's gonna stick
with me for a long time.
[Next topic]
So, I kind of
[Johnny's quirky trait]
have a bit of a unique thing going on.
What is it?
[I, Johnny, enjoy the struggle]
I kinda enjoy going through hardships.
- There's this thrill after the struggle ends
- Right, that's right.
Life… It makes me feel like I'm alive.
Since everyone's struggling here…
But I also like that
we're all suffering together.
I totally get what you mean.
[Severe memory distortion underway]
I think I'm kind of weird, actually.
- It makes us feel like a team, you know?
- Yeah.
Hey, but don't you think
we all have good chemistry together?
I just hoped it would be fun.
I couldn't imagine
what it'd be like from the lineup alone.
I still remember how awkward
I was on the first day.
[It felt so good to see a familiar face…]
But when you showed up,
I was so happy to see you.
It put my mind at ease.
That's true for me too.
Are you also the closest with
the NCT DREAM members?
I'm really the closest
with the members.
I'm like that too.
[The real reason he suddenly asked]
This thought suddenly crossed my mind.
We got close really fast.
Right?
[The secret?]
I figured it out.
It's because we went
through hardships together.
We struggled together,
and we overcame it together.
Those kinds of things are really…
[The conversation continues in the NCT room]
- It was fun, right?
- Yeah, it was fun.
[Prince Shin Dong's room
is getting ready for bed too]
(Knock)
Yes?
[The pauper citizens reappear]
Hello!
- Why?
- Why are you here?
They said there are no rooms available.
Let me just come in for now.
[The prince receives them with grace again]
Yes, yes, come on in.
It's fine. It's really fine.
- Is it okay?
- Yeah.
- Then Yo Han and I will…
- Yes.
[Then let's share a bed]
Right next to Shin Dong…!
- We'll just try lying down for a moment!
- Go ahead. Lie down.
[Let's go to bed together]
We'll just try lying here.
Go ahead, lie down.
- This is my spot, though.
- Yeah, right here.
[The burly citizens approach from both sides]
Wait, this bed actually fits us all?
It does.
[Three people lie down with no problem]
It fits, wow!
- This is nice.
- Can't we sleep like this?
All cozy and snug?
[We're actually quite close now]
Hey, this bed is seriously nice.
No, really.
[Allowing his citizens to share his bed]
Yeah, we can just sleep like this.
- For real?
- Yeah.
The two of them ended up
lying down on both sides.
But it was actually
way comfier than I expected.
[Special permission granted to save face]
I should protect my image at least.
So I told them both to sleep there.
[Teuk Dong Yo's 3-person slumber party]
So the three of us ended up sharing one bed.
Like, how can you sleep?
[Win-win]
There's no way you could sleep outside tonight.
[The prince saved the paupers' lives]
I went out here for a brief second.
The wind is blowing too hard.
It's too cold.
This won't do, Ji Sung.
I need to sleep like a prince
one last time.
[Since you're sleeping here, turn off the lights]
Let's turn off the lights.
[His first-ever prince experience ends]
Turns out, I was a prince all this time.
- Wow, this is crazy.
- Why?
[Clearly visible with the lights off]
With the lights off, this is crazy!
What's this? We turned off
the lights to sleep, and what is this?
- I wanna open the door, though.
- Let's go outside!
[Just like that, they get ready to stargaze]
[Bang!]
[He must've hit the glass door]
You hit the glass.
[Gotta see the stars even if it hurts]
Let's go out!
[Be right back]
Just stepping out for a sec!
[The two in black
and white hoodies step out quietly]
[They vanish out of sight]
I lay down to sleep when this guy was
[Chatting nonstop after stargazing]
looking at the stars, so we stepped out.
But the stars were so visible, so…
"Let's head into the desert."
[The Romantics made it all the way to the dunes]
So we went over there and back.
[Showing off the photos they took]
Honestly, it was amazing.
That day was just perfect.
I chatted with Johnny for a bit,
and then we went to see the stars.
A moment like this
might never happen again,
[A night full of great memories]
so it felt really special, and full of fun.
[Teuk Dong Yo are making
another unforgettable memory]
Can we sleep now?
Oh, is this really gonna be okay?
[The last night quietly fades away]
Should I turn off the lights, Shin Dong?
Please turn off the lights.
[The last day in Egypt]
[Johnny appears with a sagging style
first thing in the morning]
[He's here to enjoy
a relaxing cup of morning coffee]
[A morning coffee
to go with the morning Red Sea]
[While he charges up
on caffeine and romantic vibes]
[Teuk Dong Yo greet
the morning in a shocking state]
[Waking up refreshed with cries of pain]
Sleeping in the middle is so uncomfortable.
If I lean this way, there's a person.
If I lean that way, there's another.
[Sandwiched between the paupers]
Why does it feel like when I'm the prince,
I don't get that prince experience?
This is "ALL or NOTHING",
but it feels more like,
"NOTHING or NOTHING".
[Meanwhile, the real pauper is super satisfied]
I was so happy.
It was spacious, really spacious.
I turned a bit in my sleep,
and right next to me
was a super soft cushion.
Shin Dong.
[Lee Teuk's very own cushion]
At least you weren't lonely.
The bed's warm.
[Even doubles as a giant heat pack]
It could be because I'm warm.
Because I'm a warm-hearted guy.
[The final day that makes you homesick]
I want to go home.
We're leaving today.
Oh, Lee Teuk.
Open the curtain.
I'm curious what it looks like.
[Everyone wakes up with the sunlight]
Whoa, it's way too bright!
[Opening the curtains reveals…]
[A breathtaking view]
[The refreshing Red Sea under the morning sun]
[A morning gift from Giftun Island]
The water moving makes
it feel like the boat's moving.
She's iconic.
Did the rest of the guys come in?
[Johnny has a scheduled NCT 127 video call]
[Briefly switching to day job mode]
Yes.
[First showing off the beautiful view]
I'll show it to you.
[Video call topic: New comeback song]
Let's listen to it separately and meet up!
[Sincerely listening to the new song]
[The song must be a really exciting one]
[NCT 127 Taeyong]
Your energy's so high, being abroad and all.
Honestly, right now,
the view I'm seeing is
making the song sound even better.
[Happily wrapped up the meeting
thanks to the view]
[NCTZ head over to Shin Dong's room]
Good morning!
Wait, why are you here?
[Unaware of last night's drama]
You guys don't know a thing!
Oh, wow.
[To NCTZ too]
So, yesterday,
these three were
pitching their tent over there.
[Sharing the long, disastrous tale]
The wind was just way too strong.
[The unbelievable collapse
of the pauper's house]
- So they had nowhere to sleep.
- Seriously?
They begged me to let them sleep here.
[So we ended up sharing the room]
So we slept here like this.
Seriously,
yesterday was the peak of pauper life.
[Even the Paupert is shocked]
We slept really comfortably.
[Time to gear up for today's adventure]
Get ready.
[What's the grand finale mission?]
[1 hour later]
[The six guys are dragged somewhere once again]
That yellow boat looks nice.
Hey, something feels off here.
[This time, a yellow boat appears]
Doesn't it feel like it's more than just a boat?
Right? I feel like there's a catch.
I'm getting nervous.
Honestly, I'm a little scared…
[Suspicious]
Something's…
Everything is bolted down here.
Why is there an emergency exit here?
Does it drop down below or something?
[Suspicious about everything until the end]
Why would it drop below?
It wouldn't go down, right…?
[The final one]
The status missions are all done now.
That's right.
[No more missions]
No more for accommodations and things…
- Oh, they're done.
- There's no more.
You have something, though.
- If we didn't, you wouldn't do anything at all.
- That's true.
[Stating the obvious]
Please let us do some sightseeing!
We've prepared a reward
that you'll love more than anything else.
- More than anything else…?!
- Wow, what could it be?
Letting us eat the fish we catch?
- Why would we eat what we catch?
- But I am starving.
For now, just relax and enjoy the ride.
I'm so done with the boats.
If I'm being completely honest,
I want to stop getting blasted by the wind.
The wind blows too much.
[Before the whining worsens]
We've been traveling too much.
Can we just go somewhere, just us…
[The boat takes off]
It's moving, it's moving!
¡Vamos!
Let's go!
So a huge group is
supposed to ride this together, like that.
(Hello)
Oh, actually, we have a huge group too.
You have to wave like this.
You're supposed to wave back
for things like this.
[Greeting back with a dance]
Oh, there's a dancer over there!
Shouldn't we show them
what we got too?
Ji Sung, you danced
when you went to the club.
- A club?
- Yeah.
- You went to a club?
- A club?
- He went to an Egyptian club.
- That word just sounds so…
You're really into clubbing, huh?
- You're showing us so many new sides of yourself.
- I've never been to one in my life...
[Except you totally have]
[That night on Day 3 when you went all out]
In front of the cruise, oh…
I was dancing with the little kids then.
You danced with little kids at the club?
[Getting a kick out of teasing the youngest]
That's way too scandalous!
- This is bad.
- This is bad! You're gonna end up in the news!
[Innocent]
But it's really true.
- Why did the sea suddenly turn so blue?
- Probably because it's deep.
- It must be pretty deep around here.
- Oh, you're right.
It's crystal clear over there.
By any chance,
is anyone here a good swimmer?
A good swimmer…?
I can swim.
- Do you enjoy it?
- I do.
I can go in, but it's important to know
if my feet can touch the bottom.
Can you go in if you can't touch the ground?
I can't.
Will you go in if you have a life jacket?
Oh, if I have a life jacket, I can go in.
[But asking about swimming skills means…]
We're going there.
We're going snorkeling, huh?
- Yes, that's right.
- We are!
[Bingo!]
We are!
I should've practiced before coming.
[The Red Sea, the mecca for snorkeling]
[The real reason they came here
will be revealed shortly]
What kind of fish live in the Red Sea?
Tropical fish.
Then it must be warm!
Tropical fish means warm water.
They're not tropical fish because
it has the word "heat" in the name.
Then?
If it's warm… wouldn't they get cooked?
But they're tropical fish.
They usually live in warm water
around 20 to 30 degrees.
[Forget about yesterday's freezing cold]
See? I told you I was right.
[Tropical fish live in 20-30℃ water]
20 to 30 degrees for tropical fish.
- The water?
- That's really warm!
[Master of random facts]
Oh! It is!
But let's say we went in the water…
What if we get bitten?
Bitten by what?
- By piranhas.
- Piranhas?
[Master of random facts]
Then it'd go viral and be good.
[Getting bitten guarantees #1 Trending]
First of all, piranhas aren't saltwater fish.
- Oh really?
- Yes.
[Then]
What if a shark shows up?
- A shark?
- Yeah.
Perhaps that imagination of yours
is what's making you scared
of going into the water.
When I was a kid, I went to Jeju Island.
I was swimming alone, and I drifted away
to a spot where I couldn't reach the ground.
- I was thrashing around in fear…
- Yeah, I totally get that.
- and I couldn't do anything but sink.
- You can't do anything.
How did you get back?
I don't remember exactly, but at the time,
I was sinking, swallowing the water like crazy…
Seriously!
It's so vivid in my memory.
You just said you don't remember,
so what's so vivid?
- You're right.
- What does that mean?
[Such a contradictory person]
Just roll with it.
- So, my memory…
- That's strange.
That's like saying "Loudly whisper."
[Flustered]
I'm just saying!
Please just say, "Oh, really?"
Oh, really?
[Oh, yes, I see!]
So, this is Egypt!
I have no idea where we're headed.
[Before they know it,
they're in the middle of the Red Sea]
I feel like we're almost there.
I think we're here.
This is it!
[Arrived at the destination]
Alright, everyone, we're here.
- For real?
- Wow, this is the place?
First, before we explain
what today's mission is…
This boat is
actually a famous tourist attraction.
And its special feature is…
[A boat with a surprise]
right underneath the boat.
- Underneath?
- Yes.
[Is this a semi-submarine?]
Is it a submarine, by any chance?
[Correct]
That's right.
No way!
- That's amazing!
- We should've gone in earlier! It's so cold!
[Hurghada, embracing the Red Sea]
[Full of mysterious wonders]
[A pristine underwater world]
[And you get to enjoy it from inside the boat]
[Moving to the unexpected space below]
Wow, amazing!
Wow, incredible!
[Revealing the submerged area]
- Oh, it's so cold! So cold!
- Really?
[When you climb down
the stairs of the semi-submarine,]
[there are underwater windows on both sides]
[that open up to a natural aquarium right outside]
- Wow! Wow!
- This is epic!
[So cool]
There are tropical fish down there.
Hey Ji Sung!
It's a real jellyfish!
Where? Where?
Wow, they're real fish!
Wow, this is insane!
I've never seen anything like this!
- This is crazy.
- Wow, this is amazing!
[Everyone's hyped by the scene before their eyes]
This is incredible!
It's really the wild. The wild.
[Super close-up]
Wow, what is this?
[Completely losing track of time]
It's big, it's big, it's big!
Wow, there are so many fish over there!
Wow, this is totally worth seeing.
[The kidults are completely captivated]
Wow, we definitely had to come see this.
This is so great.
Seriously so great.
We weren't seeing them in an aquarium,
but from under the sea.
After going right
in the middle of the Red Sea.
It was genuinely breathtaking.
Like "I can't believe we're seeing this."
It was so cool.
Being able to see fish
without even going in the water…!
It was a whole new experience for me.
It's only possible
because the water is so clear here.
Oh, that's true.
Are they curious about us too?
I bet they're like, "What on earth is this?"
Whoa, what the heck!
That scared me!
[Laughing over the smallest things]
It just shot right up, huh?
- The two of them!
- Yeah, the two of them!
They were so dark
that it really startled me.
I feel like a kid again.
Wow, but this is really cool.
I don't think I can hold back.
I need to go in there!
I need to get in the water right now!
Wow, if we really go in…
- Hey, what's that?
- It'd be crazy.
[Completely fallen for the Red Sea]
It's really cool watching the waves above too.
The waves are really strong.
[Really enjoyed the semi-submarine tour]
So pretty.
Seriously beautiful
Amazing!
Amazing, it was really amazing.
We enjoyed everything!
Let's get going now!
What is this?
- Wow…
- What is this?
[Came back from the tour and found a safe]
Isn't this totally my specialty again?
[What is this?]
Hey, don't just push buttons. It won't work.
That was seriously amazing. Wow.
Oh, looks like there's something more.
Let's just sit down and listen, like before.
This is the grand finale mission
to wrap things up
- on our trip in Egypt.
- Wow. No way…
The moment you've all been waiting for…
6 to 0!
- Is this a team challenge?
- 6 to 0!
It's a team challenge!
Everyone succeeds together,
or everyone fails together.
[Truly bound together by fate]
Please!
And…
- You're probably curious about the reward.
- Yes
Looking at our schedule,
once we're done with today,
[Back to Cairo for the flight to Korea!]
we'll head over to Cairo
- and fly back to Seoul from there, right?
- Yes.
We'll be taking a big charter bus.
[Hurghada to Cairo]
It takes about five and a half to six hours.
[6-hour bus ride]
[1-hour flight]
That's way too long, way too long!
So! We're putting domestic
flight tickets on the line!
[Reward for success:
1-hour domestic flight tickets]
That's huge.
You probably know
since you saw it in the back.
[The safe holds the company card]
The company card's inside there.
[Flight tickets will be purchased if successful]
If we succeed, we're the only ones flying?
If you succeed, only you will be flying.
- Thank you.
- Okay, so…
The mission title is
"The Mermaid Prince's Math Class".
[The Mermaid Prince dives underwater]
Remember the windows you looked through earlier?
If you dive down
and get close to them,
[Random numbers will appear on the semi-sub window]
we're gonna show you some numbers.
[After seeing the numbers, shout them out]
After seeing the numbers,
come back up to the surface
and share what the numbers were.
With the numbers you received,
you must multiply them in your head!
[The calculated product is the code to the safe!]
The time limit is 15 minutes.
- 15 minutes?
- Yes.
I'm really bad with numbers.
I'm weak with numbers!
[Whether weak or strong, it's a teamwork mission]
It's a team mission.
The team that goes in the water!
Within your team,
the Physical Team
will handle the swimming.
And the Brain Team
will handle the math calculations.
- You have to split into those teams.
- Okay.
First, is anyone definitely on the Physical Team?
I like swimming.
- Oh, okay.
- Johnny.
I need to go into the Red Sea at least once!
Okay, anyone else?
[No one's stepping up]
No one? Johnny's the only one so far?
Okay, then Team Brain!
Raise your hands!
(Hand shoots up) (Hand shoots up) (Hand shoots up)
I'm…
(Hesitates)
I'm definitely…
(Hand shoots up)
If I had to pick between the two,
it's gotta be Brain.
Brain, definitely Brain.
I actually prepared for a PhD.
[G University
(International Commerce / PhD program dropout)]
It is possible with just one person
on the Physical Team.
- Since he can just keep looking at it.
- Right?
[15 minutes]
- But it'll take longer. - That's right.
[Need at least 2 people on the Physical Team to win]
We need at least 2 people.
So anyone who can go in the water,
please step up.
(Hmm)
You never swam in the ocean, huh?
Then, you can't.
I'm not really Team Brain or Team Physical.
It's very iffy.
But I did take a swimming class in college.
I think I got a C+.
[I guess it's up to me (C+)]
Looks like I'm the one for the job.
It's definitely better
for Lee Teuk to stay on top.
[Need more brains to calculate]
The more people on top, the faster we calculate.
Don't worry about that.
Don't worry about the calculations.
[Physical Team]
[Brain Team]
[A brief time to change]
Okay, everyone, warm up.
We've got this, we've got this!
[While they change]
Let's practice our multiplication.
Keep memorizing the times table.
[Multiplication practice led by Captain Shin Dong]
72x8.
- 8x2=16
- That's right.
[Stuck on the next step]
72.
[72x8]
574.
It's actually 576!
[It gets tricky with 3-digit numbers]
Okay, so this is how you do it.
Let's do it like this.
[Each person takes a unit's place to multiply]
You multiply the ones place.
You multiply the tens place.
[One person adds it all up]
Then, we'll pick someone who adds everything up.
Then it'll be easy.
[505x3=?]
505x3!
[Ones place]
15.
[Tens place]
0.
[Hundreds place]
15.
So what's the answer? It's 1515.
That's how you do it.
[Much easier]
Just think of it that way.
Shin Dong, that's so good.
- Are you in STEM?
- No, I'm in the humanities.
[Just classic Captain Shin Dong brilliance]
You're in the humanities?
Let's do it like this!
It works, right?
It's easy to multiply
a unit place at a time, right?
If it's like this,
I think I could even do it.
Time for the times table!
[Let's test your multiplication skills]
[7x6=?]
- What's 7x6? - 30...
- Huh?
- You're going in the water?
[Stop stalling and jump in]
It's 42, 42!
Too late! You gotta say it right away!
- We can do it if we do it like this, right?
- Yeah, we got this.
But what's really weird was…
I don't know what came over me, but…
[Multiplying single digits]
It's just multiplication,
[15 minutes for this?]
but they're giving us 15 minutes?
[Not your standard numbers]
These might not be normal numbers.
[Are there separate Egyptian numbers?!]
They could give us numbers in Egyptian numerals.
[20 minutes earlier, during break time]
I'm so hungry.
I'm hungry.
[Whining]
I'm so hungry!
- Do you need snacks?
- Yes!
[Egyptian snacks given to WANGGEOZ]
Please give us some!
Oreo!
All the food wrappers
had Arabic numerals on them.
Oreo!
Sure enough,
[The snack was printed with Arabic numerals]
it had 8 cookies inside, with 2 extra.
So it said there are 10 inside in Arabic numerals.
And on the side, there was a plus sign
followed by some Egyptian hieroglyphs.
[Egyptian numbers written on the right side]
[The Western Arabic numerals we all know]
[Meanwhile, Eastern Arabic numerals
that look like hieroglyphs]
[Egypt uses Eastern Arabic numerals]
[Looking closely]
I think this is the number 2.
[Curiosity sparks his instincts]
Is this 2? Or is this 8?
We had a conversation about this.
But?
It's just multiplication,
but they're giving us 15 minutes.
[The mission time was suspiciously long]
Huh?
[It hits him]
I've got a bad feeling about this.
[Instinct kicks in]
Let's memorize this!
[Urgently gathering all the members]
Lee Teuk, let's gather around!
(Crowding around)
Let's huddle up.
Let's come up with a plan!
From what I can tell right now,
[Instinct activated]
the passcode probably isn't a long number.
It's suspicious that they're
giving us 15 minutes for it.
[Now that you mention it, it's sus]
Right? Totally suspicious.
So the thing is,
it might not be the Arabic numbers we know.
Did you see the numbers
on the side while eating the OREO earlier?
I told you, right?
[Ji Sung also remembers the Egyptian numbers]
It looks like a 7, but it's actually a 2.
[A plausible theory]
It could be those numbers.
- Ancient numbers?
- Yeah.
[But…]
Then…
[We don't know Egyptian numbers?]
Then… Then we…
(What do we do?)
We don't know those numbers.
[Quickly search ON]
Oh my.
[Stunned by numbers they've never seen before]
How are we supposed to know this?
So Egypt has its own numbers.
Wow, I can see it!
- Wow, so cool!
- Why?
(What do you see?)
Look at this!
[On screen]
I didn't notice looking at it like this.
[If you rotate it…]
But if you look at it this way…
[Turning it around]
It says "1, 2, 3" like this!
- Oh, what?
- Right? Isn't it cool?
If you rotate it, you can see it.
[Egyptian numbers that look like hieroglyphs]
[When rotated vertically,]
[the digits look vaguely familiar]
[0 and 1 look the most similar]
It's 2 and 3, and if you rotate it,
it looks like 2 and 3.
And 4 is a flipped 3.
And 5? It's the letter O.
We pronounce 5 as "O" in Korean, so 5 is O.
And we memorized "7" as 6.
And next, "V" is 7.
We make a 7 like this with our hands, right?
So, it's 7.
And then, when it's flipped, it's 8.
And 9 looks the same.
Hey, memorize this!
[Memorizing Eastern Arabic numbers with mnemonics]
I made everyone do it 3 times!
"Hey, what is it?"
"What does it look like?"
"Write it starting from 1."
[Trusting Shin Dong's instinct, everyone starts memorizing]
For example, I'll call 4 "a flipped 3"!
I'll say it like this!
- It's 2. It's 2.
- 4 is a flipped 3.
So…
[Meticulously memorizing to prepare for the challenge]
4 is different, and 5…
If I say "7," it'll be confusing,
so I'll call it the Korean letter "gi-yeok."
Gi-yeok.
[Meanwhile, someone just stays still like a clam]
6 is gi-yeok.
5 is O.
Oh, 5 is O!
We absolutely have to pull this off, so…
I have to sit this one out!
I'm completely useless in that situation.
[His self-awareness is insane (positive)]
I'm just dead weight.
- 5 is O.
- Okay, I'll say 5 is O.
You just have to look
and tell us what it looks like.
- Just describe what you see to us.
- Got it, gi-yeok.
[The Mermaid Princes promise
to describe what they see]
[Will Captain Shin Dong's hunch be right?]
[The Mermaid Prince's Math Class]
We'll begin the Mermaid Prince's Math Class.
[Brain power]
I've got a feeling it might be 2026.
[Physical Power]
First, let's check how many digits there are.
- 2, 3…
- That's right.
[The final mission with all six members]
Flipped 4.
That's right.
[Using brains and brawn to the max]
One person solves, and the other remembers it.
[Clear the final mission]
I'll wrap this up in 5 minutes flat.
[I'm ready]
It's perfect.
[Following Captain Shin Dong, they get serious]
3x1=3, 3x2=6, 3x3=9…
3x4=12.
3x5=15.
[3x8=?]
3x8?
56?
Huh? Wait!
[Not ready for the 3 times tables...?]
Ji Sung seems a bit rusty.
You're kinda making me nervous.
[Uh…um…uh, uh…]
I'm a bit weak
with the 3 times table…
[This was filmed under expert
supervision and following safety guidelines]
Oh, why am I suddenly…
[The Mermaid Princes are ready to dive in]
Why am I suddenly feeling nervous about this?
[The mathematicians are ready to solve the problems]
Let's get on the plane!
["ALL or NOTHING" Final Mission]
[GAME START]
Here we go!
- Let's go, let's go
- We've got this!
[Mermaid Prince Johnny dives in]
- Did he go right in?
- Hey, Johnny's already down there.
[Diving fearlessly into the Red Sea]
He went already?
[Smitten]
Johnny's so cool.
[Descending below the submarine]
[Cutting through the waves without hesitation]
[Visible through the window are…]
[Eastern Arabic numerals?!]
[Johnny ascends immediately]
- Shin Dong!
- Huh?
What you predicted was spot on!
What is that?!
The Eastern Arabic numbers!
[We...]
[practiced for this!!!]
[Our instincts were spot on]
We were right. They weren't ordinary numbers.
I thought I should hurry
back up and tell the others.
Shin Dong!
[What you were thinking about]
It's the symbol you were talking about!
[was right]
[Joy]
Yes! We got this!
[Will they remember without getting mixed up?]
[The first number is "gi-yeok"]
It's gi-yeok! It's gi-yeok!
Gi-yeok? Gi-yeok?
(What number was "gi-yeok" again?)
Gi-yeok? What was gi-yeok?
No, no, no! Gi-yeok!
[I'll call 6 "gi-yeok"]
I'll call it "gi-yeok." If I say "7," it'll be confusing.
[Using "gi-yeok" for the number 6]
Oh, gi-yeok!
- I'll call it "gi-yeok."
- Gi-yeok.
6 is gi-yeok.
- 7!
- No!
[ctrl+c]
No, it's 6! 6! 6! 6! 6! 6!
[ctrl+v]
6! 6! 6! 6! 6! 6!
[Smoothly locked in the first number]
6! 6! 6!
[Off to the next number!]
(Waving around)
[Spotted an upside-down "V"]
- V! V!
- V?
[Passed the wrong information]
V? What was V again?
- V! V!
- 8!
Hold on, hold on.
- 7x8=56.
- Oh! 7! 7! 7! 6x7!
[Trusting the Mermaid Princes and starting mental math]
6x7?
[The ones place answer]
What's 6x7?
[6x7=42]
6×7=42!
[The one just now was a flipped V]
The one earlier was a flipped V!
Flipped V!
[Fortunately, they correct the error quickly]
The one earlier was a flipped V!
The second one is a flipped V?
It's 8! 8!
[6x8=?]
6x8.
[Current numbers acquired: 6, 8]
42!
[42]
6x8.
6x8, 6x8 is…
- 6x8=48.
- That's right!
[Oh…I'm getting nervous…]
Hey, something's off. Something's off.
[The Mermaid Prince
dives down to check the third number]
(Flailing)
(Charades)
[Megaphone ON]
O! O! O!
[Current numbers acquired: 6, 8, 5]
Hey, 48x5!
- O? O?
- 48 times… One person at a time!
[Ones place]
40.
[Tens place]
20.
- 240! 240! 240!
- 240!
[It's going smoothly]
This is how to do it!
6?
- 9!
- 9! 9! 9!
9 is just 9!
[Chanting together]
240x9!
[9x9 =81]
9x9 =81.
- No!
- Why?
[Questions flying]
240x9!
- You take the ones place!
- It's 0.
- Yeah, 0.
- 0! 0! 0!
[Tens place]
36.
[Hundreds place]
18.
Then what is that?
[Captain Shin Dong is overwhelmed]
Wait, hold on, I'm getting confused too.
Again, again.
[Current numbers acquired: 6, 8, 5, 9]
240x9.
- 0!
36.
- 18.
- Right.
Two thousand, one hundred…
- 2160!!
- That's it, that's it!
- We got it! Johnny, the next one!
That's it!
- There's nothing else!
- There's nothing?
[There's no next number!!!]
2160!
Huh? Seriously?
[Only 2 minutes have passed]
We're already finished?
Hold on, hold on!
[They've already got the answer!]
[Did we nail this too easily?]
Did we solve this way too easily?
Meanwhile, I was trying
to think about the symbols.
Oh, what?
- Oh, what?
- We got it!
[There's another safe!!!!]
Hey, there's another one, another one!
There's another one?
- No, there's another one, another one!
- Another one!
[If you enter the code 2160,]
[there's a smaller safe inside]
There's another safe?
Oh, come on!
[No wonder everything went so smoothly…]
No wonder!
So this is why they gave us so much time!
That's when I started
having a mental breakdown.
[The Mermaid Prince has no idea what's happening]
- Whoo-hoo!
- No! There's another one! Another one!
[Johnny... Dive back down…]
Go back down!
There's another one!
Down! Down!
[Totally thrown off by the hidden safe]
There are two doors, two doors!
There's a safe inside the safe!
[Stop talking and dive back down!]
Go down again, go down again!
[A reality that's hard to believe]
That totally caught me off guard!
There's another one, another one!
[The mathematicians are all riled up]
There's another one!
- Go back down! Go back down!
- There's another one!
[The Mermaid Princes are completely lost]
Where is it?
Go down again, go down again!
The numbers might have changed!
- They changed again?!
- Yeah! There will be more numbers!
[Diving right back down]
Go down again!
[The numbers changed?]
[They really did change!]
Flipped 3!
- Flipped 3?
- Flipped 3!
- 4!
4! Remember 4!
[Current number acquired: 4]
- Is it V?
- 2! 2!
- V!
- Oh, V!
V? V? Hold on!
- Hold on.
- The V is on the side…
V…7!
4x7 is…
[Suddenly not confident]
twenty... eight?
[Even simple math is getting confusing]
Yeah, that's right!
Yeah 28.
- Remember 28.
- 28.
[Current numbers acquired: 4, 7]
Did you see it?
- Hold on!
- Take a breath! Take a breath!
Slow down! Slow down!
We've got plenty of time!
Yo Han!
Flipped 3, V!
[But you already said those numbers…?]
Flipped 3, V?
- What does that even mean?
- Take it slow!
The third number is a flipped 3?
[In a row]
Flipped 3, V! Flipped 3, V!
[Two numbers repeat]
Wait, flipped 3 V, flipped 3 V?
- Hold up.
- 4x7=28…
- Earlier, what did we... What did we multiply?
- What was it again?
- Let's try it again.
- Yeah.
[Memory keeps resetting]
Wait, the flipped V.
Take a breather!
Wait, flipped V.
Flipped V?!
[Flipped 3 and V]
Flipped 3, V! Flipped 3, V!
[Flipped V]
Wait, Flipped V.
[The miracle of turning a V into a flipped V]
Flipped V?
That's when I started
having a mental breakdown.
Was it a V or a flipped V?
It started getting confusing.
I was really thrown off then.
[Chaos brought on by Captain Shin Dong]
Flipped… Wait, sorry! If it's a flipped V…
It's 8, it's 8!
- 8, 8! That's right! It's 8!
- It's 8, 8!
- 8!
- Let's…
Let's start with the big numbers first. 8x8.
[Starting with a random number]
4x4= 16.
24.
- 24?
- Yeah.
[Yelling loudly]
Yo Han! Say it!
[The quiet clam suddenly gets loud]
Flipped 3? Flipped V?
- 256x4?
- It's just 3?
Wait, Lee Teuk! Lee Teuk!
It's 256x4.
(Zero doubts)
256x4!
24!
- 24!
- 20!
- 8!
- 200!
I'm getting confused. Hold on.
[Counting fingers]
20.
[True math pros]
24? You have to do it like this.
- 24, 24,
- Okay, 24 here.
- 1024, 1024.
- 1024.
[Dashing off with the wrong answer]
Hey, wait, wait, wait.
[Of course it doesn't work]
It's not! It's not! It's not!
[Flustered]
It's not 1024!
Why isn't it?
How's your energy holding up?
[It's good]
One more time! From the start…!
Can you please do it one more time? Sorry!
[Thanks to the mathematicians, the Mermaid Princes are struggling...]
The number's wrong right now!
Wow... Johnny's seriously crazy, for real.
He's a seal!
He's so good! So good at swimming!
[Flexing his swim moves]
He's so good.
(4747)
It's right!
- (4848) It's right?
- It's right? He said it's right.
[Still mixing up V with flipped V]
But a flipped V is 8, right?
It's 8, yeah.
Flipped 3 is 4!
Then it's 4488.
What was V again?
- Just a regular V?
- Yeah.
It's not a flipped V?!
[Frustrated]
Flipped 3! Regular V!
[Finally cleared the miscommunication]
Then it's 7! 7!
- 7x7 is…
- 49!
[Now it's just simple math!]
7x7=49
[Multiply 49 by 4!]
Alright, multiply by 4!
Multiply by 4!
[Ones place]
4x9=36.
[Tens place]
16.
One thousand… Oh…
146(?)
146x4…
- 24.
[The math blunder continues like a curse]
16.
16, 16.
- Lee Teuk.
- 4.
[Something's off]
Let's multiply one more time, just in case.
- Take a break!
- 7x7.
[Again, again]
Let's start with 49x4!
[Stuck on repeat]
49x4!
[Forever stuck on 49x4...]
9x4=36
36, 36! Remember 36! 36!
- 16.
- 16?
[Correct]
Then it's 196.
196, right?
- Huh?
- Is it 4?
Please do your best!
You can do it!
Wait, hold on...
Don't talk to me!
What's next?
[Blank stare...]
Lee Teuk, what is it?
Lee Teuk, come on!
- What?
- Lee Teuk, what is it when you multiply it?
- I thought mine was 4.
- 4? Then…
596...?
[Wrong]
It's not it!
- Let's try again!
- What is this?
Again.
Johnny, just check one more time...!
[....ha]
- You sure about this?
- I'm positive!
But why did they keep
telling me to double-check?
I figured they were
struggling with the math.
Because I kept going down
and checking multiple times.
Lee Teuk, I'm sure…
This is right...!!
Johnny! Just go one more time…!
Tell us again from the first number!
Tell us from the start and then go!
[Endlessly checking the exact same numbers]
Flipped 3.
Flipped 3. Shin Dong, flipped 3.
- V!
[Working hard to relay the numbers]
Flipped 3.
- V!
Yeah, that's right.
7744.
[Yo Han watches all the chaos unfold]
[C+ swimmer is on the move]
After I got used to diving,
I was able to go in a bit more easily.
[Confirming with his own eyes]
Johnny!
There's one more V!
Really?!
Wait, hold on!
There's one more V?!
[There are more numbers?]
There's one more V!
Oh, there's one more V?
Then hurry up and take a look!
[Johnny dives back down to double-check]
If we mess up again this time,
we can't unlock it for the next 5 minutes.
Double-check carefully and let us know!
[I'll handle this round]
Because Johnny's tired, Yo Han is...
He's going in himself!
- Lee Teuk!!
- Yeah?
- Flipped 3!
- Yeah.
- V!
- Flipped 3!
- Yeah.
- V!
- It's the same.
[What's gotten into everyone...?]
What's up with him?
(What I said)
It's right.
- (What I said) It's right, right?
- Yeah.
[Confident]
There was one more V.
Yo Han was actually a risk factor.
Our workload doubled because of him.
[Bright smile]
I have to say what I saw too, right?
[When Johnny spoke,]
When Johnny said, "Flipped 3!"
[he just did his best to repeat it]
Then I'd do the same, "Flipped 3!"
Flipped V!
Flipped 3!
I was just repeating what he said.
Alright, 5 minutes left!
Hey, why aren't you doing it!
No, this is just...!
Seriously...! Something feels off...
I suddenly didn't want to do it anymore.
No matter what we did,
we couldn't solve the second problem.
[Deeply stuck in the 7x7=49 swamp]
7x7 is definitely 49.
- It's 49, right?
- Yeah.
And then you multiply it by 4.
- 9x4=36.
- 36.
[Wait a sec...]
Then it's 196.
No, wait! Hey!
Our math is wrong!
It should come out
to like 200-something?!
- Yeah, look.
- Oh, really? Our math is wrong?
[Spiraling again...]
7x7=49.
No, just take 49
and multiply it by 4.
- 4x9=36.
- That's right.
- 4x4=16.
- So then...
It's 206!
- Why is it 206?
- 49x4 is...
[Chills]
There's no way it's 200...?
[That number can't possibly come out...?]
4x4=16.
How could it be 200?
- Take the 200...
- It's 196. 196!
- Yeah, it's 196.
- It's 196.
- Just multiply 196 by 4.
- Times 4.
[6x4=24]
6x4=24.
Ah, 4x6...
- Is it not?
- With 194...
[Brain suddenly stops]
- 3.
- 4x5=20.
4x5=20!
Ah, 24! 24! Sorry!
[You said it correctly 10 seconds ago]
And multiply it by 4.
6x4=24.
[Mistakenly thinking he's wrong]
Did you mess up then?
- I messed up!
- Oh, really? 24. Okay!
[DAWN, you weren't wrong...]
24. Okay! 24.
- I was wrong, I was wrong.
- You were the one messing up.
[Tens place]
36!
Yeah, 36.
[Hundreds place]
Mine is 4.
Then...?
Oh, this is confusing.
784?
It's 784?
[Will this painfully calculated number be correct?]
Please let there be no more inside.
[It opened!]
Okay!
We got it! We got it!
Is it over?!
Did we get it?
[Let's hurry home
and make up for lost time...!]
Please, please!
[Excited]
Hey! Hey!
Quick! One more time!
One more time!
[Waaah, I'm a baby lock]
Ugh... Seriously, I...!
This is driving me crazy...
How many numbers is it?
- 4 numbers.
[The Mermaid Princes who were
watching what was happening above]
[dive in at the same time]
When I went in a third time,
it became a mental battle at that point.
"I have to do this..."
That's when my muscles started getting sore...
[His energy started running out]
The waves kept crashing,
so I had to use even more energy.
- It must be so hard for Johnny.
- I seriously feel so bad!
- Flipped 7!
If it's a Flipped 7, then it's 6.
- Flipped 7 is 6.
- Yeah, 6.
[Getting faster with repetition]
- Flipped V.
Flipped V?
- 8.
- 8?
8?
- 7x8!
- 7x8.
7x8=56!
[Literally a moment ago...]
Flipped 7!
If it's a flipped 7, then it's 6.
[After saying it was a 6]
Flipped 7 is 6.
8.
[They forgot again...]
8? 7x8.
7x8=56!
- 9.
- 9 is 9!
- 56x9!
[Calculating with wrong numbers again...]
56x9...
- 9x6 is...
- 54.
6x9=54.
- 45.
[ALL or NOTHING]
- 504?
- I still remember up to 504.
[ALL or SILLY]
504!
504, 504, 504,
504, 504, 504...
9 was the last one, right?
There's one more "siot."
[Yo Han suddenly says there's a Korean character?]
Our workload doubled because of him.
[Diving back in to re-check the numbers]
There are only 3 numbers, though?!
There are no more?
- There are only 3!
- There are only 3?
[The lock needs 4 numbers]
[There are only 3 numbers?]
There are no more? There are only 3?
Should we try 0-504? 0-504?
054…
[0504 / 5040]
0504.
[Trying with zeroes in the front and back]
There's gotta be a zero either in front or back.
- It's not, it's not.
- Then...
- Should we try the other way?
- The opposite way.
It's not opening.
Can you please check one more time?
[Prince Yo Han's on it]
Yo Han's really good at this now!
[Cutting through the current
and checking thoroughly]
- Hold on.
- Yeah.
Take your time!
[Yo Han's number: 8]
"Siot"!
"Siot"?
- Flipped V!
- Oh, flipped V!
And then...
[Yo Han's numbers: 8, 9]
9!
- 8, 9.
- 6x9=54.
[Yo Han's numbers: 8, 9, 8]
Flipped V!
Oh, it's 8, 9?
8x9=72!
[The numbers are different from Johnny's?]
8x9=72.
- And then?
- Flipped V!
[Going back to verify]
- It's like that?
- 8, 9, 8?
- Is it 8, 9, 8? 8, 9, 8?
- It's 8, 9, 8!
8x9?
[I'm pretty sure I saw it correctly...]
[Panicked]
Oh, Lee Teuk! Lee Teuk! Lee Teuk!
The first one!
- It's a sideways 3!
- Sideways 3?
It's 3! It's 3!
[The number Johnny confirmed]
[Shaped like a 3 on its side,]
[the number 3]
[But when he first saw the number]
- Flipped 7!
[Mixing up the two numbers]
3-8-9!! 3-8-9!! Then...
[Recalculating with the new number]
What did we have at the beginning?
[Current numbers: 3, 8, 9]
Was it 7, 8, 9?
- No, it's not.
- It was 8x9=72.
Ugh... Why can't I remember this?
[Echoing]
3x9... Then it's...!
- Then it's 3...!
- Ugh, it's so noisy here…
- 9! What was it?
- Why is everyone loud here...?
- 3!
- 9!
[So chaotic...]
Flipped V!
[Echoing loudly]
3, 8, 9! 3, 8, 9!
3x8!!
3x8=24!
[Something's off…]
Is it 3, 8, 9?
Wasn't it 4 numbers earlier?
- Again!
- No, they said there were only 3!
Oh, but!
Why did Yo Han say it was 8, 9, 8...?
Why did he say 8, 9, 8?
[Happily clueless]
3, 8, 9?
Please look one more time!
I'm sorry!
[Giving up...]
Something's wrong! It won't open.
- 1 minute left!
- There's only 1 minute left!
3x8 is...
- 8x9=72.
- 72.
What is this?
But I did make a mistake there.
I didn't see that
there was another number at the end.
[That number that caused all the confusion]
[What Johnny saw]
It's a sideways 3!
Flipped V!
9!
[What Yo Han saw]
"Siot"!
9! Reversed V!
[Just need to combine
everything they said together]
There's another flipped V!
- Another flipped V!
- See? See?
- 216! 216!
- Multiply 216 with...
[The value of 216x8 is the answer]
8!
6x8 is?
[Ones place]
6x8=48
[Tens place]
80!
Wait a sec, 80...
- So just 80...
- Yeah, just 80.
[Hundreds place]
16.
1886...?
You said it's 1200?
Okay, 30 seconds!
[Time's running out]
Let's try it again one more time.
6x8 is?
48.
[48+80]
80.
[48+80=128]
128! 128! What's yours, Lee Teuk?
I got 16!
2x8=16!
[128+1600=17...]
1, 7...
10!
- 9!
- 1, 7, what is it?
- 8!
- 48.
- 7!
- You're 8, right?
[Game Over]
It's not working!
[Bewildered]
Is it over?
The Mermaid Prince's Math Class.
Wait, wait. Just wait.
- The final mission...!
- Wait! Just wait!
[Mission Failed]
You have failed.
[This has to be a lie.....]
- Why isn't it right?
- Wait a minute.
[Can't let it go]
6x8=48, isn't it?
Yeah.
[The Mermaid Princes who worked the hardest]
You did so well!
- You really did!
- We're sorry!
No, no.
We're the ones
who couldn't calculate it.
Was multiplication always this hard?
Sit down, sit down.
I think it's warmer in the water.
Just sit here for now.
- How did it go?
- Are you okay?
- We... We couldn't do it.
- We failed, we failed.
- We failed.
- Really?
The numbers were right.
- We were such fools!!
- Why? What went wrong?
[Figured out the answer afterwards]
128+1600... Why?
Why couldn't I figure this out?
1728. I did this earlier, didn't I?
[Got really close to the answer]
We went with 48 earlier.
- Oh, we went with 48?
- Ugh, what an idiot move...!
[I'm such an idiot...]
I was such a fool...
Oh!
I was unlocking it the wrong way.
It presses down like this,
[Captain Shin Dong misunderstood the unlocking method]
so I thought you had to press and pull.
But because I pressed and pulled,
it didn't work. Such a fool!
[What a bummer]
Then we were right earlier.
You just had to pull it.
Customer, you worked so hard!
[Applause for the hard-working Mermaid Princes]
You two really worked hard.
- For real.
- It's such a shame, though!
Hey, I'm so sorry.
I'm really sorry.
To explain to the Physical Team
who worked hard down there,
the team up here
just couldn't do the math.
- Oh, were we wrong?
- You found all the right numbers.
[Reason for failure: Terrible math skills]
They just couldn't do the math.
Yeah, that's right.
I kept saying 4x6=26.
How is 4x6 even 26?
[Q. What caused the failure?]
The people up there!
6x4=24!
Even I know that!
[I'd be a brainiac with that too]
I got at least that much brain power.
Honestly, I felt kind of sorry as well, so…
[Just left feeling a little disappointed]
It just ended with "What a bummer."
But of course!
4x6 definitely isn't 26...
I'm gonna look like
a total idiot on this show.
They did all the multiplying,
and I was the one who couldn't add.
I wanted to go on "The Devil's Plan".
What do I do now?
No one's gonna cast me now.
That's what I was thinking.
I'm not blaming anyone, but…
I think DAWN had a really bad headache.
If we failed because of me,
the person who made me fail was Lee Teuk.
Lee Teuk just needed to focus on his part.
"What is it?"
"The tens place!"
[Booming voice]
4, 8, 9!! 4, 8, 9!! 3x8 is?
[Intimidated]
3x8=24!
No! I got them pumped up instead!
6x8!
Get it together!!
That's just an excuse.
We just couldn't do the math.
Lee Teuk just kept shouting,
"What is it? What is it?" next to me,
and I suddenly got so confused.
I kept thinking,
"Man, I wish he'd just be quiet."
I'm hitting the slate!
1, 2, 3!
[Time to say goodbye now]
Great job! Great job, everyone!
It's a shame. Like, it would've been nice
if it ended with us all shouting,
"Success! Whoo!"
[Regrets]
Such a shame.
It wasn't important
whether we took the bus or the plane,
it just would've been great
if we wrapped up with cheering.
This is fun!
It really is fun!
Is 15 minutes always this fast?
Why'd it go so fast?
The boat as well…
Going back feels so much faster
than when we headed out.
I think so too.
The wind is blowing nicely too.
The journey back usually feels faster,
no matter what it is.
[That strangely long first day of the trip]
When I saw the Pyramids I'd only seen
in books as a kid right before my eyes,
"So, those are the Pyramids!"
[And the ever-changing fate every day]
It felt like the clouds were hugging me.
How long do we have
to stay as paupers?
I'm going to be a prince today.
[Standing somewhere between hardship and romance]
That night was the absolute worst of the worst.
My mouth has no saliva left,
but I'm just gonna sleep.
[Just laughing together]
Me too.
I think this is the most
memorable moment of this trip.
[A week that flew by in a flash]
It's truly mystical.
It's so beautiful.
After traveling together for almost a week,
we got to know each other
and grew closer together.
The thought "I'm sad that I'm a pauper"
didn't matter after the first day.
It just felt like we were on a fun trip together,
so I really enjoyed it.
[And]
[a shy reflection of the trip]
After traveling…
It's really fascinating, because…
[What I'm left with]
Honestly, Egypt was really great,
["These people"]
but I feel like I gained people,
and I really loved that.
Before we departed,
I was actually really worried,
because it's basically
my first time traveling with friends.
[With their first-ever travel mates,]
A totally weird combo.
[they threw awkward questions to each other]
You're really strong! Are you still working out?
No, no.
I really tried hard to get close
and thought a lot about it.
[Making those worries pointless]
The older members made everything so comfortable.
[we blended so perfectly together]
The younger guys were so nice too.
[While solo trips are great,]
Traveling is honestly
[it was way better together]
double the fun when you do it with others.
I actually like getting lost.
I'm the type who's fine with detours
as long as there's a destination.
And on this trip, we took a lot of detours.
(Throbbing headache)
(A serious detour)
I shouldn't have eaten that ramyeon…
Ugh! I'm so annoyed!
[But even after taking the long way around
or ending up as paupers again,]
It's okay.
It's fine, even if we take a detour.
[What this trip left behind,]
I think it's going to
["A trip that's worth all the detours"]
stay in my memories. I had so much fun.
I had so much fun!
It was hard, and we suffered together,
but because we suffered together,
I think it made us closer faster.
[Even when dumped in the middle of a harsh desert]
Just how far…
Can people see where we are?
[The first night lying side-by-side stargazing]
Wow! I can see the stars!
Whoa, this is crazy!
[When we're together, even hardships turn romantic]
I really love this moment now.
This is what romance is.
Because I had gotten
comfortable with the guys,
I was able to let
my guard down during the filming.
[What they gained after coming this far]
I think our chemistry
[A connection they'd love to see again anytime]
as six was incredibly great.
To me, "happiness" is just…
Laughing!
[We laughed a lot, so we must be very happy]
Laughing is happiness, and we laughed a lot in Egypt.
When else...
would I get to do something like this?
I kept thinking,
"I'm so glad 'ALL or NOTHING'
was my first variety show."
Personally,
this will stay with me
for a very long time.
I feel like I've done so many firsts this year.
That's great!
Everything's more fun
when it's your first time!
Exactly.
And I think people grow really quickly.
Definitely.
[How much you've grown]
[isn't really important]
[Now,]
[with the friends we met in this unfamiliar place,]
I think I learned what traveling is all about.
Oh, so this is how you're supposed to travel!
[we are heading back with great memories]
This is fun!
"ALL or NOTHING". Paupers and Princes.
Season 2!
Look forward to it!
(Peace)
1!
2!
3!
[It's now time to bring this journey to an end]
Great job, everyone!
Ohh… Thank you for all your hard work!
[Though this bizarre trip is over,]
1, 2, 3!
[we're heading back to where it all began]
Save me, please.
[After failing the mission,
they go on the 7-hour bus ride]
I really became a pauper today…
[Saying goodbye now feels bittersweet]
This is crazy.
We're still filming "ALL or NOTHING".
[But we look forward
to the day we meet again]
[Mountains may never meet,
but people always will]
[Thank you to everyone
who tuned in to "ALL or NOTHING"]